Guide to the Mabel Loomis Todd Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1879-1932; Series II; 14 linear feet (33 boxes)
  - General Correspondence
    - Clark, Myra S. (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Clarke, Christopher, 1915, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Clarke, James F., 1929 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Coa-Cop, 1894-1926, undated (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Cobb, Charles W., 1916-1929 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Coe, Anna C., 1930, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Coe, Ernest Francis (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Coffin, Caroline R. (Mrs. Charles A.), 1897-1908 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Coffin, Jenny M., 1895-1896, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Colby, Ellen C., Circa 1890-1910 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Colby, Harriet F., 1893-1898, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Colt, Helen B., 1916-1931, undated (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Colt, Josephine D. (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Colvocoresses, Harold, 1927-1929 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Conant, Mary E., 1899, 1913, undated (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Conant, N. (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Conant, Nelly F. (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Cook, G.H., 1895-1910 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Cook, Joseph L., 1909 (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1924, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Cooper, Elizabeth (Mrs. Clayton S.), 1924-1932 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Cor-Cu, 1893-1931 (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Corona Typewriter, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 146)
    - Corwine, Dessie M., 1909-1915 (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Cowles, Emma M., 1916-1922 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Cowles, Sara B. Johnson (Mrs. Herbert T.), 1896-1929, undated (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Crawford, Harriet E., 1917-1930 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Crawford, Harriet Cutler (Box 10, Folder 150)
      See also: box 92, folder 10.
    - Crawford, Jessie H. (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Curtis, Kate S. (Mrs. Cyrus H.K.), 1931 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Cutler, James T., 1906-1910 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Cutler, Suzie Mann (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Cutter, H. Maria, 1879-1892 (Box 10, Folder 153)
      See also: box 1, folder 6.
      See also: box 92, folder 12.
    - Da, 1882-1932 (Box 10, Folder 154)
    - Dakin, Arthur Hazard, 1908-1929 (Box 10, Folder 155)
    - Dakin, Emma S. (Mrs. Arthur H.), 1911-1923, undated (Box 10, Folder 156)
    - Darby, Edward A., 1906-1914 (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - Darby, Kathryn E. (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - Darby, Margaret (Box 10, Folder 157)
    - Darling, Adella F., 1893, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - Darling, Margaret (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - Darling, Mary Letchworth (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - De, 1896-1928 (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - Deane, Rachel, 1900, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 160)
    - Decker, Sarah S. Platt, 1927, undated (Box 10, Folder 161)
    - Deering, James, 1911, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 162)
    - Deering, Marion, 1922-1924, undated (Box 10, Folder 163)
    - DeHaven, Mrs. Alice Smith, 1925-1931 (Box 10, Folder 164)
    - Deland, Margaret, 1900 (Box 10, Folder 165)
    - Deming, Caroline S., 1898-1909 (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - Deming, Constance (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - Deming, Horace E. (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - DeVilbiss, Lydia Allen, 1930, undated (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - Dewey, Melvil, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 168)
    - Di-Do, Circa 1880-1932 (Box 10, Folder 169)
    - Dickinson, Edward, Undated (Box 10, Folder 170)
    - Dock, Margaret, 1922-1925 (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - Dole, Nathan Haskell, 1904-1930 (Box 10, Folder 172)
    - Dolley, Charles S., 1922, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 173)
    - Donald, Cornelia, 1889-1901 (Box 10, Folder 174)
    - Donald, Winchester (Box 10, Folder 174)
    - Dorsey, Isabel Lovell (Mrs. Grafton D.), 1906, 1907, undated (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - Doughan, Bertha, 1900-1906 (Box 10, Folder 176)
    - Doughan, May (Box 10, Folder 176)
    - Douglas, Marjorie Stoneham, 1922-1928 (Box 10, Folder 177)
    - Downer, Sophie, 1899-1931, undated (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - Dr-Dy, 1892-1932 (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - Draper, Anna Palmer (Mrs. Henry), 1889-1912, undated (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Draper, Amos G., 1880-1899 (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - Draper, Bell M. (Mrs. Amos G.) (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - Driver, Elizabeth, 1920-1936 (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Drose, Mary R., 1925, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - E, 1883-1929, undated (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - Eastman, Anna Day, 1907-1932 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Eastman, D. (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Eastman, Elaine G. (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Ellis, Clara B., 1910 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - Ellis, Clara Spalding, 1904-1906 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Ellsworth, Lucy, 1899-1920 (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Ellsworth, William W. (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Ely, Caroline Weir, Circa 1880-1888, undated (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Ely, Grace (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Ely, L. B. (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Emerson, Anna Seelye, Undated (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Emery, Stephen A., 1881-1888 (Box 10, Folder 191)
    - Eskine, John, 1903-1911 (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - Eskine, Pauline (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - Fa-Fi, 1900-1929, undated (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Fairchild, Marian, 1920-1928 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Field, Harriet T. (Mrs. Barnum H.), 1890-1906, undated (Box 11, Folder 195)
    - Field, Louise B., 1919, 1920, undated (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Field, William P., 1926-1932 (Box 11, Folder 197)
    - Fisher, Mr. & Mrs. George E., 1890, undated (Box 11, Folder 198)
    - Fitch, William Clyde, Circa 1880 (Box 11, Folder 199)
    - Fl-Fu, 1890-1931 (Box 11, Folder 200)
    - Fleming, Caroline, 1906-1911, undated (Box 11, Folder 201)
    - Foote, Katherine, 1908-1915 (Box 11, Folder 202)
    - Foote, Katherine M. (Box 11, Folder 202)
    - Forbes, Susan E.P., 1897-1902 (Box 11, Folder 203)
    - Foster, Bertha, 1925-1931 (Box 11, Folder 204)
    - Foulke, Mary F.R., 1929-1931 (Box 11, Folder 205)
    - Foulke, William Dudley (Box 11, Folder 205)
    - Fowler, Georgiana W. (Mrs. Horace W.), 1891-1906, undated (Box 11, Folder 206-207)
      See also: box 18, folder 473.
    - Francis, Helen Page, 1932, undated (Box 11, Folder 208)
    - Francke, Marie-Louise Embree, 1925-1928 (Box 11, Folder 209)
    - Freeman, Alden, 1929, 1932, undated (Box 11, Folder 210)
    - Ga-Gi, 1899-1931 (Box 11, Folder 211)
    - Galloupe, Sarah A., 1891 (Box 11, Folder 212)
    - Gam, Gertrude, 1891, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 213)
    - Gates, Florence Vincent, 1880-1900, undated (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Gates, Lansford (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Gates, Margaret (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Gates, Mary C. (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Gates, Merrille (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Gates, Merrille, Jr. (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Gibson, Albert, 1927-1931 (Box 11, Folder 215)
    - Gifford, Emma (Mrs. George), 1924-1932 (Box 11, Folder 216)
    - Gillette, Grace James, 1904-1921 (Box 11, Folder 217)
    - Gl-Go, 1885-1926, undated (Box 11, Folder 218)
    - Glidden, Emily, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 219)
    - Glidden, Etta H., 1897-1905 (Box 11, Folder 220-229)
    - Glidden, Etta H., 1906-1930, undated (Box 12, Folder 230-237)
    - Glidden, Harold, 1908-1927 (Box 12, Folder 238)
    - Glidden, Lucy Emma (Box 12, Folder 238)
    - Goodrich, Charles N., 1894-1895 (Box 12, Folder 239)
    - Gordon, Winifred Campbell, 1905, 1906, undated (Box 12, Folder 240)
    - Gorgas, William C., 1907, 1908 (Box 12, Folder 241)
    - Gortshore, Jessie Evelyn, 1905, 1906 (Box 12, Folder 242)
    - Gosse, Elizabeth Merrill, 1896-1910 (Box 12, Folder 243)
    - Gr-Gu, 1888-1930 (Box 12, Folder 244)
    - Graham, Margaret (Mrs. Howard Spencer), 1920, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 245)
    - Grandin, Grace H. (Mrs. John Livingstone), 1911-1921 (Box 12, Folder 246)
    - Gray, Lydia B. (Mrs. D.D.), 1926-1932 (Box 12, Folder 247)
    - Green, Clare Bellinger, 1929, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 248)
    - Greenwall, Mary Hallock, 1905-1909 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - Grey, W.H., 1900 (Box 12, Folder 250)
    - Griffith, Harriet D., 1900-1902 (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - Griffith, Lucy J. (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - Griffith, Sally May (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - Groff, D.A., 1914-1931 (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - Groff, Dorothy Mixter (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - Groff, Grace M. (Mrs. P.W) (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - Groff, Ulysses G. (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - Grosvenor, Edwin A., 1892-1896 (Box 12, Folder 253)
    - Grosvenor, Lillian W., 1896, 1898, 1909, undated (Box 12, Folder 254)
    - Gruenberg, Eugene, 1904-1908, undated (Box 12, Folder 255)
    - Ha, 1888-1931 (Box 12, Folder 256)
    - Haden, Florence P., 1923-1924, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 257)
    - Hailman, J.D., 1925-1926 (Box 12, Folder 258)
    - Hailman, Johanna K.W (Box 12, Folder 258)
    - Hale, Edward E., 1894, 1898 (Box 12, Folder 259)
    - Hale, Ralph T., 1908, 1910,1921, 1923-1924, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 260)
    - Hall, Florence Howe, 1894, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 261)
    - Hall, Mary Lee, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 262)
    - Hall, S. Stanley, 1897-1898 (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - Halliwell, Ashleigh C., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - Hammond, Fanny Reed, 1898, 1910-1911, undated (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Hammond, William C. (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Hardy, Caroline, 1898, 1919, 1924, undated (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Hare, Mary Theresa, 1898, undated (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Harris, Edward, 1900, undated (Box 12, Folder 268)
    - Harris, Elizabeth R.B. (Mrs. Edward) (Box 12, Folder 268)
    - Harris, George, 1899-1921, undated (Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Harris, George, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Harris, Jane (Box 12, Folder 269)
    - Haskell, Elizabeth, 1904, 1910, 1929, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Haskell, Florence (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Haskell, H.N. (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Haskell, Juliana (Box 12, Folder 270)
    - Havens, Kate C. (Mrs. T.C.), 1925-1930 (Box 13, Folder 271)
    - He-Hi, 1882, 1891-1898, 1905-1906, 1919-1927, undated (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Head, Elizabeth, 1893-1909, undated (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Head, Katherine (daughter of Franklin Head) (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Head, Franklin, 1893, 1911, undated (Box 13, Folder 274-280)
    - Heade, M.J., 1882, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 281)
    - Headley, Phineas C., 1905 August-1920, undated (Box 13, Folder 282-288)
    - Heaton, Ellen M., 1885-circa 1900s, undated (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - Hersey, Heloise E., 1896-1905 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - Higginson, Mr. & Mrs. Thomas Wentworth, 1892, 1895, 1905-1912, undated (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - Hilder, Howard, 1919-1924 July (Box 13, Folder 292-302)
    - Hilder, Howard, 1924 October-1932 (Box 14, Folder 303-313)
      See also: box 123, folder 61.
    - Hilder, John C. ("Jack"), 1927-1931 (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - Hilder, John C., Jr. (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - Hilder, Wendy (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - Hill, Alice S., Circa 1880s-1896 (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - Hill, Clara Sibley (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - Hill, A.S., 1887-1917, undated (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Adelaide (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Alice (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Caroline (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Ellen (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Henry F. (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, L.D. (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Mary P. (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hill, Susan Clapp (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - Hillyer, [Robert?], 1923 (Box 14, Folder 317)
    - Himchman, Lydia S. (Mrs. Charles S.), 1909 (Box 14, Folder 318)
    - Hinsdale, Katherine S., 1894-1927 (Box 14, Folder 319)
    - Hitchcock, Bedford W., 1883-1891 (Box 14, Folder 320)
    - Hitchcock, Mary E., 1901-1903, undated (Box 14, Folder 321)
    - Ho, 1890-1925 (Box 14, Folder 322)
    - Hoar, Mary, 1880, 1883 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - Hoge, Mary S., 1927-1932, undated (Box 14, Folder 324)
    - Hoitt-Howland, Alice May, 1907, 1908, undated (Box 14, Folder 325)
    - Holden, Edward S., 1893, 1900 (Box 14, Folder 326)
    - Holland, Carrie, 1889-1925 (Box 14, Folder 327)
    - Holland, W.J. (Box 14, Folder 327)
    - Hollingsworth, Polly R. (Mrs. George), 1903-1906 (Box 14, Folder 328)
    - Hollingsworth, Rose (Box 14, Folder 328)
    - Hooper, E.G., 1881-1883 (Box 14, Folder 329)
    - Hoover, Clara, 1882 (Box 14, Folder 330)
    - Hopkins, Margaret S. Briscoe, 1895-1898, undated (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - Houghton, Henry, 1927-1929, undated (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - Houghton, Lucile (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - Houghton, Mifflin and Company, 1890, 1897, 1902, 1909, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 333)
    - Howe, Julia Ward, 1895-1905 (Box 14, Folder 334)
    - Howells, Elinor, Undated (Box 14, Folder 335)
    - Howells, Mildred (Box 14, Folder 335)
    - Howells, William Dean, 1890-1893, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 336)
    - Howland, Anna P., 1906-1913, undated (Box 14, Folder 337)
    - Howland, Florence E. (Box 14, Folder 337)
    - Hoxie, Ruth Norcross (Mrs. Richard L.), 1919-1927 (Box 14, Folder 338)
    - Hu-Hy, 1890-1925 (Box 14, Folder 339)
    - Hubbard, Alice (Mrs. Elbert), 1900-1915 (Box 14, Folder 340)
    - Hubbard, Elbert (Box 14, Folder 340)
    - Hubbard, Benjamin, 1928-1931 (Box 15, Folder 341)
    - Hubbard, Elizabeth Wright (Box 15, Folder 341)
    - Hubbell, Rose Strong, 1923, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 342)
    - Hudson, Mary Clemmer Ames, 1884 (Box 15, Folder 343)
    - Huggins, Lady Margaret Lindsey, 1885-1901 (Box 15, Folder 344)
    - Huggins, Sir William (Box 15, Folder 344)
    - Hunt, Rachel (Mrs. Roy Arthur), 1930 (Box 15, Folder 345)
    - Huntington, Elizabeth W., 1918-1923 (Box 15, Folder 346)
    - Hyde, Anna F., 1892-1903, undated (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - Hyde, Loman C. (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - Hyde, Loman N. (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - Hyde, Mary S. (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - Hyde, William De W., 1902-1912 (Box 15, Folder 348)
    - Inagaki, K., 1896-1930 (Box 15, Folder 349)
    - Ingham, Mary H., 1903, 1904, undated (Box 15, Folder 350)
    - Iwado, T., 1910 (Box 15, Folder 351)
    - Ivanovsky, Alexandra, 1924-1931 (Box 15, Folder 352)
    - Ivanovsky, Catharina (Box 15, Folder 352)
    - J, 1894-1925 (Box 15, Folder 353)
    - James, Arthur Curtiss, 1896-1932 (Box 15, Folder 354-362)
    - James, D. Willis, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 363)
    - James, Ellen S. (Mrs. D. Willis), 1896-1916, undated (Box 15, Folder 364-370)
    - James, George Wharton, 1904, 1906 (Box 15, Folder 371)
    - James, Harriet P. (Mrs. Arthur), 1895-1931, undated (Box 15, Folder 372-377)
    - James, Helen E., 1898-1914, undated (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - Jeans, Sir James, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 379)
    - Jefferis, William M., 1903-1906 (Box 16, Folder 380)
    - Johnson, Burgess, 1919, undated (Box 16, Folder 381)
    - Johnson, Constance (Mrs. Burgess) (Box 16, Folder 381)
      See also: box 17, folder 430.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth B., 1910-1911, undated (Box 16, Folder 382)
    - Johnson, Ellen G., 1910 (Box 16, Folder 383)
    - Johnson, Laura C., 1916-1917, undated (Box 16, Folder 384)
    - Jones, Cora C.S., 1903, 1906, undated (Box 16, Folder 385)
    - Jones, Maria Hoppin, Undated (Box 16, Folder 386)
    - Jones Library, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1922-1932 (Box 16, Folder 387)
    - Jordan, Mary A., 1891-1898 (Box 16, Folder 388)
    - Ka-Ki, 1884-1932 (Box 16, Folder 389)
    - Kasebier, Gertrude, 1907, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 390)
    - Keep, Austin Baxter, 1897-1932 (Box 16, Folder 391)
    - Keep, Wallace Huntington (Box 16, Folder 391)
    - Kendrick, Georgia A., 1897-1900 (Box 16, Folder 392)
    - Kennan, Eveline Weld, 1889-1931 (Box 16, Folder 393)
    - Kilberne, Katherine Skinner, 1911, undated (Box 16, Folder 394)
    - Kilbourne, Mary P., 1917-1929, undated (Box 16, Folder 395)
    - Kimball, Arthur L., 1910, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 396)
    - Kin, Yamel, 1888-1903, undated (Box 16, Folder 397)
    - King (J.B.) Transportation Co., 1916 (Box 16, Folder 398)
    - Kingsbury, Susie Shaw, 1879-1896 (Box 16, Folder 399)
      See also: box 1, folder 29.
    - Kite-Powell, Eleanor C. (Mrs. T.L.), 1926-1931 (Box 16, Folder 400)
    - Kite-Powell, Stephen K. (Box 16, Folder 400)
    - Kittredge, Helen M., 1890-1898, undated (Box 16, Folder 401-402)
    - Kittredge, Helen B., 1903, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 403)
    - Kittredge, Karrie, 1890 April-1892 March (Box 16, Folder 404-409)
    - Kittredge, M.T., 1907-1909, undated (Box 16, Folder 410)
    - Kl-Ku, 1888-1929 (Box 16, Folder 411)
    - Kline, Minerva, 1905, 1906 (Box 16, Folder 412)
    - Kojima, K., 1897-1925 (Box 16, Folder 413)
    - Kraft, E.A., 1905-1910, undated (Box 16, Folder 414)
    - Kraft, Nancy Irwin Louis (Mrs. E.A.) (Box 16, Folder 414)
    - La, 1879-1924, undated (Box 16, Folder 415)
    - Ladd, J. Herley, Circa 1890-1894 (Box 16, Folder 416)
    - Laighton, Cora Rutherford (Mrs. Paul), 1918-1929 (Box 16, Folder 417-419)
    - Laighton, Florence, M., 1929 (Box 16, Folder 420)
    - Laighton, Paul DeBlois, 1924-1926 (Box 16, Folder 421)
    - Lailer, Frank A., 1911-1932 (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Lane, Bertha Palmer (Mrs. William C.), 1903, 1906, 1923-1931 (Box 17, Folder 423)
    - Lane, Margaret, 1923-1924, undated (Box 17, Folder 424)
    - Lane, Rosamond (Box 17, Folder 424)
    - Lane, William C. (Box 17, Folder 424)
    - Le, 1889-1923 (Box 17, Folder 425)
    - L'Ecluse, Julia Maubry Weeks (Mrs. Milton), 1925-1930 (Box 17, Folder 426)
    - Lee, Sara White, 1895, undated (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Lee, Sophia E., 1895-1913 (Box 17, Folder 428)
    - Lenmon, Isobel H., 1879-1929 (Box 17, Folder 429)
      See also: box 1, folder 17.
    - Leslie's Weekly, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 430)
      See also: box 16, folder 381.
    - Li-Ll, 1894-1933 (Box 17, Folder 431)
    - Little, Nellete Reed (Mrs. William C.), 1920-1929, undated (Box 17, Folder 432)
    - Little, William V., 1928 (Box 17, Folder 433)
    - Lo, 1893-1932 (Box 17, Folder 434)
    - Loeb, James, 1894-1903 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Loeb, Nina J. (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Long, Agnes, 1912, 1915, undated (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Longfellow, Alice M., 1901 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Longyear, John M., 1907-1917, undated (Box 17, Folder 438)
    - Longyear, Mary Beecher (Mrs. John M.) (Box 17, Folder 438)
    - Lord, Annie Hooper, 1885-1891 (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Lord, Florence, 1893 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Lothrop, Margaret, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Lothrup, Harriet M., 1895-1905 (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Loveman, Robert, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Lowell, Amy, 1922-1925 (Box 17, Folder 444)
    - Lowell, Constance S. (Mrs. Percival), 1895-1919 (Box 17, Folder 445)
    - Lowell, Percival (Box 17, Folder 445)
    - Lu-Ly, 1905-1930 (Box 17, Folder 446)
    - Luce, Alice H., 1904, 1905, undated (Box 17, Folder 447)
    - Lyman, Albert J., 1891-1911, undated (Box 17, Folder 448)
    - Lyman, Elizabeth Mills (Box 17, Folder 448)
    - Maa-Mac (Box 17, Folder 449)
    - MacCord, Mary Hudson, 1887-1903 (Box 17, Folder 450)
    - MacDonald, Georgia A., 1893 (Box 17, Folder 451)
    - MacMillan Company, 1897, 1923-1924 (Box 17, Folder 452)
    - McMillen, Ellen, 1927-1929, undated (Box 17, Folder 453)
    - Mag-Maz, 1887-1903 (Box 17, Folder 454)
    - Maltby, Elizabeth M., 1898, 1899, undated (Box 17, Folder 455)
    - Mana-Zucca, 1927-1931 (Box 17, Folder 456)
      See also: box 88, folder 11.
      See also: box 89, folder 12.
    - Marriot, Henry, 1903-1919 (Box 18, Folder 457)
    - Marsh, E.D., Circa 1880-1906, undated (Box 18, Folder 458)
    - Marsh, Elizabeth C. (Mrs. Dwight W.) (Box 18, Folder 458)
    - Marshall, Frank H., 1905, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 459)
    - Marshall, Sophia Hall (Mrs. Frank H.) (Box 18, Folder 459)
    - Matheson, Anna M. (Mrs. William J.), 1917-1928 (Box 18, Folder 460)
    - Matheson, May (Box 18, Folder 460)
    - Matheson, William J. (Box 18, Folder 460)
    - Maxwell, Annie, 1898, undated (Box 18, Folder 461)
    - Mayo, Gertrude, 1926-1930 (Box 18, Folder 462)
    - Me-Ml, 1888-1929, undated (Box 18, Folder 463)
    - Means, Carroll A., 1928 (Box 18, Folder 464)
    - Means, Philip (Box 18, Folder 464)
    - Meeker, Helen Painter, 1918-1929 (Box 18, Folder 465)
    - Meiklejohn, Alexander, 1913, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 466)
    - Meiklejohn, Nannie L. (Mrs. Alexander) (Box 18, Folder 466)
    - Merrill, Mary S. (Mrs. John F.), 1896-1906, undated (Box 18, Folder 467)
    - Milinowski, Arthur, 1904-1916, undated (Box 18, Folder 468)
    - Milinowski, Harriet (Mrs. Arthur) (Box 18, Folder 468)
    - Milinowski, Marta, 1904-1919 (Box 18, Folder 469-470)
    - Miller, Olive Thorne, 1894, 1895 (Box 18, Folder 471)
    - Mills, Ardella, 1900-1912, undated (Box 18, Folder 472)
    - Mills, Elizabeth (Box 18, Folder 472)
    - Mills, Georgiana Adams, [1896?]-1931 (Box 18, Folder 473)
    - Miner, Edward F., 1909-1912 (Box 18, Folder 474)
    - Mitchell, Annie, 1922-1930 (Box 18, Folder 475)
    - Mitchell, Lucy Sprague, 1912, 1913, undated (Box 18, Folder 476)
    - Mitzlaff, Margarette von, 1894-1912 (Box 18, Folder 477)
    - Mo-Mu, 1894-1930 (Box 18, Folder 478)
    - Monnier, Mathilde, 1903-1908 (Box 18, Folder 479)
    - Moore, Elsie Clark (Mrs. James A.), 1922-1931 (Box 18, Folder 480)
    - Moore, James A. (Box 18, Folder 480)
    - Morse, Alice E., Undated (Box 18, Folder 481)
    - Morse, Anna G. (Box 18, Folder 481)
    - Morse, Anson D., 1897, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 482)
    - Morse, Edward S., 1896-1901 (Box 18, Folder 483)
    - Morse, Margaret (Mrs. Anson D.), 1897, 1913, undated (Box 18, Folder 484)
    - Morse, Sarah D. (Box 18, Folder 484)
    - Morse, William Northrup (Box 18, Folder 484)
    - Morton, Sadie Galloupe, 1891 (Box 18, Folder 485)
    - Moulton, C.W., 1889-1899 (Box 18, Folder 486)
    - Moulton, Louise Chandler, Undated (Box 18, Folder 487)
    - Munro, Lillie Barr, 1928, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 488)
    - Munro, Patty (Box 18, Folder 488)
    - Munroe, Everett, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 489)
    - Munroe, Mabel Stearns Noble (Mrs. Kirk), 1901-1923 (Box 18, Folder 490-495)
    - Munroe, Mabel Stearns Noble (Mrs. Kirk), 1924-1930 (Box 19, Folder 496)
    - Munroe, Mary Barr (Mrs. Kirk), 1917-1922 (Box 19, Folder 497)
    - Murray, Mary (Mrs. Gilbert), 1912 (Box 19, Folder 498)
    - Murrell, Mrs. Hagar A., 1904-1910 (Box 19, Folder 499)
    - Na-Ne, 1891-1932 (Box 19, Folder 500)
    - The Nation, 1882-1907 (Box 19, Folder 501)
    - Neill, Abby R. (Mrs. H.H.), 1883-1892 (Box 19, Folder 502)
    - Neill, H. Humphrey (Box 19, Folder 502)
    - New England Automobile Journal, 1909-1910 (Box 19, Folder 503)
    - Newcomb, Emily Kate, 1879, 1883, 1888, 1889 (Box 19, Folder 504)
    - Newcomb, Mary (Mrs. Simon), 1884-1885, 1889, 1893 (Box 19, Folder 505)
    - Newcomb, Simon, 1890, 1906, undated (Box 19, Folder 506)
    - Ni-Nu, 1893-1930, undated (Box 19, Folder 507)
    - Niles, Lousia F., 1906-1907 (Box 19, Folder 508)
    - Nitze, Anina Hilken, 1907-1915, undated (Box 19, Folder 509)
    - Noble, Everett Stearns, 1910-1930 (Box 19, Folder 510)
    - Norton, Katherine Garrison (Mrs. Charles), 1891-1928, undated (Box 19, Folder 511-513)
    - Nourse, Emma J., 1893, 1895 (Box 19, Folder 514)
    - Noyes, Katherine, Undated (Box 19, Folder 515)
    - Nugent, Florence B, 1922-1925 (Box 19, Folder 516)
    - O, 1894-1920 (Box 19, Folder 517)
    - O'Brien, Gertrude, 1897-1914, undated (Box 19, Folder 518-522)
    - O'Brien, Minni J., 1904, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 523)
    - O'Connor, Ellen M., 1882-1883 (Box 19, Folder 524)
    - O'Connor, Jean, 1880-1882 (Box 19, Folder 525)
    - Okie, Lily V., 1889-1891 (Box 19, Folder 526)
    - Old, George D., 1905 (Box 19, Folder 527)
    - Olds, Marion E. (Mrs. George D.), 1892-1897, 1923, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 528)
    - Osgood, Robert Bayley, 1894-1915 (Box 19, Folder 529)
    - Otterson, Josephine C., 1896, 1907 (Box 19, Folder 530)
    - Otterson, Lucy (Box 19, Folder 530)
    - Oumiroff, Boza and Ellen Spravka, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 531)
    - The Outlook, 1899, 1906, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 532)
    - Owen, Ruth Bryan, 1920-1926 (Box 19, Folder 533)
    - Pa-Pe, 1892-1931 (Box 19, Folder 534)